<?xml version="1.0"?>
<days>
    <day date="2025-06-01">
        <photos>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54564610731_8a47b9dbdd_b.jpg">
                <alt>Lamps in a small city park at night.</alt>
                    <caption>
                        There's a jazzy mural in the Lilypad and it reminds me
                        of the sort of painting my parents and grandparents have
                        in their house: musicians rendered cubistly, frenetic
                        atmosphere. Let the good times roll. You can make a
                        whole career off that sort of art; it's very
                        commercially viable, very pretty. And why not? I'm pretty sure
                        aesthetics are fascist&mdash;expecially when profound
                        confrontation of modernity is recast as nostalgic
                        kitsch&mdash;but wouldn't it be cool to live
                        in a Parisian fantasy? And the whole world is a
                        painting by Monet...
                        <br/>
                        <br/>
                        Oh yes. That's been done. By Monet.
                    </caption>
            </photo>
        </photos>
    </day>

    <day date="2025-05-30">
        <photos>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54555547417_a348fc0764_b.jpg">
                <alt>Dark stormclouds over darker trees next to the facade of a brick-and-stone building.</alt>
                <caption/>
            </photo>
        </photos>
    </day>

    <day date="2025-05-22">
        <photos>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54556666333_979dc06e6b_b.jpg">
                <alt>Worm on wet stone</alt>
                <caption/>
            </photo>
        </photos>
    </day>
    <day date="2025-05-17">
        <photos>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54531548845_7ffc6979f6_b.jpg">
                <alt>Tree canopy against a partly cloudy sky</alt>
                <caption>Picnic, looking up!</caption>
            </photo>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54531389294_9a6d46f01f_k.jpg">
                <alt>Tree canopy against a partly cloudy sky</alt>
                <caption/>
            </photo>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54531548850_bd8599d2ed_k.jpg">
                <alt>Tree canopy against a partly cloudy sky</alt>
                <caption/>
            </photo>
        </photos>
    </day>
    <day date="2025-05-13">
        <photos>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54520018426_804fc122e8_c.jpg">
                <alt>Woman sitting in a train with a book watching blurred green trees go by.</alt>
                <caption/>
            </photo>
        </photos>
    </day>
    <day date="2025-05-11">
        <photos>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54520204433_cbe8f926d4_c.jpg">
                <alt>A wooded hillside in early morning.</alt>
                <caption/>
            </photo>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54519081597_5347f414de_c.jpg">
                <alt>A tree with green and white leaves against a blue early morning sky, a stone wall in the background.</alt>
                <caption>
                    If only I had made a photograph of the burning incense's
                    twirling smoke, or the stone walls of Morningside, or the
                    rock on which we danced. I was entirely present for the
                    magic of those moments.
                </caption>
            </photo>
        </photos>
    </day>
    <day date="2025-05-03">
        <photos>
            <!-- cityscape -->
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54497035854_0e93e5484e_c.jpg">
                <alt>The Boston skyline at night.</alt>
                    <caption>
                        Having lived in larger cities, Boston often underwhelms
                        me. But sometimes I look at the skyline over the water
                        at night and I think of the scale of it, how many people
                        occupy those lighted rooms, this human-concrete machine,
                        how much ground I can cover in a day on the T, and I
                        feel in awe, and very lucky to be here.
                    </caption>
            </photo>

            <!-- mit power plant -->
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54497035809_f829599713_c.jpg">
                <alt>A power plant at night, in black and white.</alt>
                <caption/>
            </photo>
        </photos>
    </day>
    <day date="2025-04-26">
        <photos>
            <!-- street tree -->
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54477716562_15ee48331d_c.jpg">
                <alt>A close-up of the bright green leaves of a tree planted on the sidewalk of a street.</alt>
                <caption>
                    My phone doesn't work these days.
                </caption>
            </photo>

            <!-- parking lot tree -->
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54478555126_94a5bd0631_c.jpg">
                <alt>A white-blossomed tree next to factory windows on a brick wall.</alt>
                <caption>
                    It is seven years old. It is slow and buggy when I try to
                    take photos. I've gotten in the habit of carrying my old
                    Fujifilm camera (eleven years old) for everyday use.
                </caption>
            </photo>

            <!-- other park tree bokeh -->
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54478910205_d2090d4390_c.jpg">
                <alt>An out-of-focus shot of a tree at twilight, with bokeh caused by the lights hanging from the tree.</alt>
                <caption>
                    Aside from forcing me to slow down and be deliberate when I
                    take photos, using the Fujifilm has the odd effect of
                    closing the gap between "casual" smartphone camera use and
                    the pretension of "professional" DSLR or mirrorless cameras.
                </caption>
            </photo>

            <!-- street -->
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54478839673_8c05f05cf7_c.jpg">
                <alt>A residential street at twilight.</alt>
                <caption>
                    <!-- hipster feeling? -->
                    I'm using this fancy device to take pictures that are
                    intended to be nothing more than impressions of what I see
                    during the day, which I send to my friends. But it goes the
                    other way, too: this curious habit, negotiated by the camera
                    with all its fiddly settings and its "professional" affect,
                    is dignified beyond fleeting record and elevated to <em>craft</em>.
                    There's a ritual to it: take photos, get home, look through, and
                    <em>then</em> send them off.
                </caption>
            </photo>

            <!-- park light -->
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54478757264_b7874b76d6_c.jpg">
                <alt>A lamppost in a park at twilight, causing lens flare</alt>
                <caption>
                    The whole process takes more thought and effort, and I'm not
                    sure that's a bad thing.
                </caption>
            </photo>
        </photos>
    </day>

    <day date="2025-02-22">
        <photos>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54345222495_cb407d5d3a_k.jpg">
                <alt>Squirrel Brand Company building. There is snow. There is an empty community notice board in the foreground.</alt>
                <caption/>
            </photo>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54345222490_4542ad8419_k.jpg">
                <alt>A community garden covered in snow.</alt>
                <caption/>
            </photo>
        </photos>
    </day>

    <day date="2024-12-28">
        <photos>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54232343102_dbbf70f126_k.jpg">
                <alt>Yellow temporary utility markings on wet concrete. They indicate property lines.</alt>
                <caption>I read about utility markings in <em>99% Invisible Cities</em> and now I see them everywhere.</caption>
            </photo>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54233486443_7a3fc43629_k.jpg">
                <alt>A brick wall with a window into a half-basement office with a table and plant.</alt>
                <caption/>
            </photo>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54233659305_16e2de0690_k.jpg">
                <alt>Barren trees next to a classical building on an overcast day.</alt>
                <caption>Been trying to find other ways to record my feelings.</caption>
            </photo>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54233256651_d9a3728656_k.jpg">
                <alt>Ducks on the Charles River. Boston is covered in fog in the background.</alt>
                <caption/>
            </photo>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54232343087_435db88d27_k.jpg">
                <alt>A window. There is a tree in the foreground with eerily lit branches hanging down.</alt>
                <caption/>
            </photo>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/54233659275_51aa5038a4_k.jpg">
                <alt>A person sits working in an empty classroom across a patch of grass.</alt>
                <caption>Oh, to be working in an empty classroom over the holidays!</caption>
            </photo>
        </photos>
    </day>

    <day date="2024-08-11">
        <photos>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/53917456916_ae67911866_k.jpg">
                <alt>Colorado mountain vista</alt>
                <caption/>
            </photo>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/53917902250_699ef56991_k.jpg">
                <alt/>
                <caption/>
            </photo>
            <photo link="https://live.staticflickr.com/65535/53917456931_0fa9fee593_k.jpg">
                <alt/>
                <caption/>
            </photo>
        </photos>
    </day>
</days>
